<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <FALCFF.EnableModDesc>If this mod is causing problems, please log a bug and disable it from here untill an update is available, so as to preserve your settings.</FALCFF.EnableModDesc>
  <FALCFF.EnableMod>Enable Mod</FALCFF.EnableMod>

  <FALCFF.ShowTargetingOverlay>Show targeting overlay</FALCFF.ShowTargetingOverlay>
  <FALCFF.ShowTargetingOverlayDesc>When manually targeting a ranged weapon, highlight all tiles the projectile could pass through, accounting for miss radius.</FALCFF.ShowTargetingOverlayDesc>

  <FALCFF.ProtectPets>Protect Pets</FALCFF.ProtectPets>
  <FALCFF.ProtectPetsDesc>Protect trained animals with an assigned master, the same way colonists are protected.</FALCFF.ProtectPetsDesc>

  <FALCFF.ProtectColonyAnimals>Protect All Tame Animals</FALCFF.ProtectColonyAnimals>
  <FALCFF.ProtectColonyAnimalsDesc>Protect all tame animals belonging to the colony. May cause performance issues on lower end machines with large numbers of livestock.</FALCFF.ProtectColonyAnimalsDesc>

  <FALCFF.IgnoreShieldedPawns>Ignore pawns with active shield belts</FALCFF.IgnoreShieldedPawns>
  <FALCFF.IgnoreShieldedPawnsDesc>Shooters will not worry about pawns wearing a shield belt with at least 10% power standing in the line of fire.</FALCFF.IgnoreShieldedPawnsDesc>

  <FALCFF.EnableWhenUndrafted>Always enable when undrafted</FALCFF.EnableWhenUndrafted>
  <FALCFF.EnableWhenUndraftedDesc>If you tend to disable the 'Avoid Friendly Fire' setting on pawns during combat, using this option will ensure it is always turned back on again when they are undrafted.</FALCFF.EnableWhenUndraftedDesc>

  <FALCFF.EnableAccurateMissRadius>Use accurate miss radius</FALCFF.EnableAccurateMissRadius>
  <FALCFF.EnableAccurateMissRadiusDesc>Low skill shooters have a larger miss radius than higher skilled ones and this mod accounts for that. If this setting is disabled, the mod will assume a one tile miss radius for all shooters, which will be more lenient to low skill shooters but may result in more friendly fire hits.</FALCFF.EnableAccurateMissRadiusDesc>
</LanguageData>
